BRAC Additional Records 5488 C
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 342-432 (Box 33)
  - Lodge 394 and 407 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 411, 1921 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Bakken-Grimes-Kalligher-Miller (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 425, 1960 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 425 Extra Information (1 of 3) (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 425 Extra Information (2 of 3) (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 425 Extra Information (3 of 3) (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 426, 1922 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 432, 1932 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- 438-639 (Box 34)
  - Lodge 438, 1962-1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 442, 1939-1973 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 444, 1960-1971 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    January 1960-October 1971
  - Lodge 446, 1962-1973 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 456, 1941-1973 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 461, 1922-1972 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 462, 1928-1974 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 463, 1941-1973 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 478, 1923-1973 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 479, 1938-1973 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 482, 1938-1973 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 483, 1953-1974 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 484, 1922-1974 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 486, 1963-1970 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 490, 1959-1970 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 494, 1943-1971 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 496, 1934-1969 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 507, 1961-1973 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 515, 1941-1969 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 516, 1924-1972 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 533, 1972-1973 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 534, 1935-1972 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 535, 1935-1970 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 542, 1921-1973 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 554, 1963-1969 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 556, 1935-1973 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 563, 1947-1974 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 575, 1921-1973 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 595, 1956-1972 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 600, 1922-1974 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 601, 1951-1975 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 605, 1932-1971 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Lodge 616, 1948-1973 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Lodge 623, 1922-1973 (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Lodge 625, 1949-1973 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Lodge 634, 1938-1972 (Box 34, Folder 36)
- 640-799 (Box 35)
  - Lodge 640, 1946-1974 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 647, 1963-1970 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 652, 1946-1972 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 657, 1937-1970 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 680, 1937-1972 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 681, 1922-1972 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 683, 1936-1973 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 687, 1948-1971 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 689, 1931-1975 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 701, 1928-1972 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 704, 1937-1972 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 707, 1949-1972 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 731, 1941-1974 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 738, 1938-1973 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 748, 1941-1971 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 750, 1921-1975 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 757, 1924-1973 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 764, 1921-1973 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 765, 1946-1973 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 769, 1938-1970 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 770, 1932-1973 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 772, 1931-1972 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 773, 1941-1973 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 788, 1939-1973 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 791, 1923-1972 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 793, 1939-1973 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 799, 1937-1972 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 800, 1939-1973 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 806, 1922-1972 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 808, 1929-1970 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 811, 1921-1972 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 815, 1970-1973 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Lodge 817, 1939-1973 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Lodge 827, 1921-1972 (Box 35, Folder 34)
- 800-999 (Box 36)
  - Lodge 835, 1938-1974 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 839, 1933-1973 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 840, 1959-1974 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 850, 1937-1973 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 850 - Appeal: R. Martinello, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 851, 1938-1973 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 856, 1945-1973 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 864, 1939-1973 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 871, 1937-1973 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 873, 1937-1971 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 876, 1963-1969 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 874, 1939-1973 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 877, 1937-1970 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 879, 1922-1972 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 889, 1937-1973 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 890 - Moore and DeMartini Case, 1964-1966 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 890 - Appeal: William C. Heath, 1967-1968 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 890, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 890 - Appeal: Sam Stein, 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 890, 1966-1971 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 898, 1926-1973 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 903, 1941-1971 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 909, 1939-1972 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 912, 1948-1972 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 913, 1924-1969 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 924, 1941-1972 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 928, 1937-1972 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 940, 1939-1975 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 950, 1932-1973 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 967, 1937-1970 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 974, 1937-1975 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 986, 1960-1969 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Lodge 992, 1962-1974 (Box 36, Folder 33)
- 1000-1139 (Box 37)
  - Lodge 1004, 1938-1973 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 1013, 1960-1972 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 1014, 1941-1972 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 1022, 1930-1974 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 1024, 1922-1972 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 1026, 1958-1972 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 1027, 1941-1968 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 1028, 1922-1972 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 1029, 1963-1972 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 1037, 1921-1973 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 1038, 1921-1973 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 1042, 1941-1974 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 1045, 1963-1969 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 1053, 1941-1974 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 1055, 1941-1974 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 1057, 1938-1975 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 1058, 1942-1972 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 1059, 1942-1974 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 1060, 1941-1973 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 1066, 1946-1972 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 1078, 1942-1972 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 1080, 1942-1971 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 1092, 1927-1973 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 1095, 1942-1969 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 1098, 1942-1972 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 1100, 1956-1970 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 1102, 1947-1969 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 1104, 1948-1972 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 1109, 1960-1974 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 1110, 1943-1973 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 1112, 1943-1971 (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 1119, 1943-1969 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Lodge 1123, 1943-1971 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Lodge 1124, 1926-1972 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Lodge 1129, 1944-1971 (Box 37, Folder 35)
  - 1132, 1944-1973 (Box 37, Folder 36)
  - Lodge 1133, 1944-1971 (Box 37, Folder 37)
  - Lodge 1136, 1923-1974 (Box 37, Folder 38)
  - Lodge 1143, 1922-1972 (Box 37, Folder 39)
- 1140-1299 (Box 38)
  - Lodge 1145, 1946-1974 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 1146, 1945-1974 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 1150, 1943-1970 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 1157, 1946-1973 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 1167, 1946-1972 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 1170, 1950-1973 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 1176, 1946-1974 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 1178, 1946-1974 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 1179, 1946-1974 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 1183, 1961-1974 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 1190, 1921-1971 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 1192, 1949-1972 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 1193, 1921-1973 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 1198, 1929-1974 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 1205, 1958-1973 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 1212, 1958-1974 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 1223, 1921-1961 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 1232, 1949-1974 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 1234, 1921-1969 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 1238, 1926-1974 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 1240, 1949-1973 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 1248, 1922-1973 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 1256, 1947-1970 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 1257, 1950-1969 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 1260, 1931-1971 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 1262, 1958-1963 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 1262, 1964-1969 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 1265, 1950-1969 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 1280, 1950-1973 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 1285, 1950-1972 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 1287, 1923-1973 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 1288, 1933-1972 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- 1300-1499 (Box 39)
  - Lodge 1300, 1949-1972 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 1303, 1955-1972 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 1305, 1951-1973 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 1307, 1951-1973 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 1314, 1951-1973 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 1316, 1951-1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 1317, 1952-1972 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 1324, 1952-1971 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 1338, 1944-1972 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 1334, 1952-1973 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 1337, 1923-1974 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 1343, 1960-1973 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 1349, 1953-1970 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 1356, 1922-1972 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 1358, 1954-1972 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 1359, 1954-1972 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 1366, 1922-1973 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 1367 - Appeal of C.E. Grable, 1967 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 1372, 1929-1975 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 1373, 1956-1970 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 1378, 1949-1974 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 1383, 1956-1974 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 1385, 1957-1974 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 1386, 1957-1973 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 1390, 1929-1972 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 1399, 1942-1972 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 1401, 1945-1973 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 1403, 1960-1973 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 1404, 1963-1972 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 1434, 1927-1967 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 1440, 1931-1974 (Box 39, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 1453, 1921-1972 (Box 39, Folder 32)
- 1500-1699 (Box 40)
  - Lodge 1511, 1930-1975 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 1517, 1935-1973 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 1527, 1941-1971 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 1528, 1947-1972 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 1530, 1960-1971 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 1533, 1947-1970 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 1539, 1942-1971 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 1540, 1946-1971 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 1542, 1945-1971 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 1550, 1941-1971 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 1552, 1944-1971 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 1553, 1945-1971 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 1556, 1945-1970 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 1557, 1941-1971 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 1558, 1946-1971 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 1559, 1945-1971 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 1560, 1944-1972 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 1563, 1947-1971 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 1568, 1942-1971 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 1570, 1943-1972 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - 1572, 1947-1972 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 1573, 1966-1971 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 1574, 1945-1972 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 1575, 1941-1962 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 1576, 1947-1970 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 1579, 1943-1971 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 1580, 1945-1971 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 1582, 1947-1976 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 1583, 1946-1969 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 1585, 1941-1970 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 1586, 1945-1972 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 1587, 1947-1972 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Lodge 1588, 1947-1971 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Lodge 1590, 1947-1972 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - Lodge 1597, 1946-1971 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Lodge 1599, 1961-1970 (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - Lodge 1600, 1947-1973 (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Lodge 1601, 1939-1971 (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Lodge 1605, 1943-1973 (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Lodge 1608, 1936-1973 (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - Lodge 1612, 1935-1973 (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Lodge 1616, 1946-1973 (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Cone Lodge 1617, 1971-1975 (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Lodge 1628, 1946-1973 (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - Lodge 1631, 1947-1973 (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Lodge 1634, 1941-1973 (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Lodge 1642, 1937-1972 (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Lodge 1645, 1949-1971 (Box 40, Folder 48)
- 1700-1789 (Box 41)
  - Lodge 1701, 1944-1972 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 1708, 1946-1972 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 1709, 1944-1967 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 1710, 1946-1972 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 1712, 1942-1969 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 1717, 1946-1972 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 1718, 1947-1971 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 1719, 1946-1971 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 1721, 1946-1971 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 1722, 1947-1971 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - 1723, 1952-1971 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 1724, 1940-1971 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 1725, 1945-1972 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 1727, 1945-1971 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 1730, 1946-1969 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 1733, 1947-1971 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 1734, 1944-1972 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 1736, 1944-1970 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 1741, 1947-1971 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 1749, 1943-1968 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 1751, 1948-1972 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 1754, 1947-1972 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 1755, 1940-1972 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 1756, 1946-1971 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 1757, 1947-1971 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 1758, 1947-1971 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 1759, 1947-1972 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 1766, 1947-1972 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 1769, 1962-1971 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 1773, 1947-1972 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 1774, 1946-1971 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 1775, 1945-1970 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Lodge 1776, 1947-1972 (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Lodge 1777, 1947-1971 (Box 41, Folder 34)
  - Lodge 1778, 1945-1970 (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Lodge 1779, 1960-1972 (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Lodge 1780, 1940-1971 (Box 41, Folder 37)
  - Lodge 1783, 1945-1971 (Box 41, Folder 38)
  - Lodge 1784, 1941-1972 (Box 41, Folder 39)
  - Lodge 1785, 1946-1969 (Box 41, Folder 40)
  - Lodge 1786, 1941-1971 (Box 41, Folder 41)
  - Lodge 1787, 1944-1971 (Box 41, Folder 42)
- 1790-2019 (Box 42)
  - Lodge 1791, 1945-1972 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 1793, 1944-1971 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 1795, 1942-1972 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 1796, 1944-1972 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 1798, 1953-1970 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 1799, 1941-1972 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 1800, 1941-1971 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 1801, 1947-1972 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 1805, 1943-1962 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 1903, 1969-1972 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 1903, 1973-1975 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 1904, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 1912, 1969-1972 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 1917, 1969-1974 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 1922, 1973-1975 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 1924, 1973-1975 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 1926, 1973-1974 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Local Lodges - Fruit Growers Express, 1974-1975 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    October 1974-July 1975
  - Lodge 1931, 1969-1974 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 1934, 1969-1971 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 1938, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 1950, 1969-1971 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 2001, 1947-1973 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 2003, 1948-1973 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 2004, 1961-1969 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 2004, 1970-1974 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 2004 - Paul Robinson: Appeal, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 2004 - Paul Robinson: Appeal Concerning the Eligibility of Brother V.L. Gough Being a Candidate for General Chairman, 1968 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 2005, 1963-1974 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 2006, 1944-1972 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 2007, 1928-1974 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 2008, 1961-1974 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Lodge 2009, 1925-1974 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - Lodge 2010, 1934-1974 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Lodge 2011, 1953-1973 (Box 42, Folder 35)
  - Lodge 2013, 1927-1973 (Box 42, Folder 36)
  - Lodge 2014, 1924-1973 (Box 42, Folder 37)
  - Lodge 2016, 1922-1974 (Box 42, Folder 38)
  - Lodge 2017, 1928-1974 (Box 42, Folder 39)
  - Lodge 2018, 1926-1974 (Box 42, Folder 40)
  - Lodge 2019, 1939-1974 (Box 42, Folder 41)
- 2020-2049 (Box 43)
  - Lodge 2021, 1945-1970 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 2023, 1926-1974 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 2024, 1964-1974 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 2025, 1922-1959 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 2026, 1922-1973 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 2027, 1929-1974 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 2028, 1959-1974 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 2029, 1958-1974 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 2030, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 2031, 1923-1973 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 2032, 1923-1972 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 2033, 1922-1972 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 2035, 1966-1974 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 2035 - Work File of Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express and Station Employees, 1968-1974 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 2036, 1938-1973 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 2037, 1963-1974 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 2038, 1930-1974 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 2040, 1959-1974 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 2041, 1922-1974 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 2042, 1922-1974 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 2043, 1962-1974 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 2045, 1961-1974 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 2046, 1925-1974 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 2048, 1957-1974 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 2049, 1959-1974 (Box 43, Folder 25)
- 2050-2079 (Box 44)
  - Lodge 2051, 1922-1974 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 2052, 1963-1974 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 2054, 1941-1973 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 2055, 1922-1973 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 2056, 1922-1974 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 2057, 1949-1974 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 2058, 1963-1974 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 2060, 1921-1974 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 2061, 1961-1972 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 2063, 1963-1972 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 2064, 1962-1972 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 2064 - Discipline: C.A. Tomany, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 2064 - Discipline: G.G. Paulsen, Junior, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 2064 - Discipline: L.A. Archbold, 1966 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 2067, 1963-1974 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 2068, 1923-1974 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 2069, 1940-1974 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 2070, 1946-1974 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 2071, 1925-1975 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 2072, 1961-1972 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 2073, 1921-1974 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 2074, 1962-1974 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 2075, 1963-1974 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 2076, 1936-1974 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 2079, 1946-1974 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 2080, 1930-1974 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- 2080-2139 (Box 45)
  - Lodge 2081, 1925-1974 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 2082, 1963-1972 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 2083, 1922-1972 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 2084, 1929-1972 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 2085, 1932-1974 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 2086, 1948-1969 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 2087, 1963-1974 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 2088, 1931-1974 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 2089, 1970-1973 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    Temporary File
  - Lodge 2090, 1922-1973 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 2092, 1946-1973 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 2094, 1924-1972 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 2095, 1935-1974 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 2097, 1944-1973 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 2098, 1929-1974 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 2099, 1929-1974 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 2100, 1956-1974 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 2101, 1929-1974 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 2102, 1960-1974 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 2103, 1923-1974 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 2107, 1925-1973 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 2108, 1933-1974 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 2110, 1959-1974 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 2111, 1951-1974 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 2112, 1924-1973 (Box 45, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 2113, 1926-1974 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 2114, 1946-1974 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 2115, 1922-1974 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 2117, 1943-1973 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 2119, 1944-1974 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 2121, 1942-1973 (Box 45, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 2123, 1921-1974 (Box 45, Folder 32)
  - Lodge 2125, 1949-1973 (Box 45, Folder 33)
  - Lodge 2127, 1921-1974 (Box 45, Folder 34)
  - Lodge 2128, 1922-1974 (Box 45, Folder 35)
  - Lodge 2130, 1958-1974 (Box 45, Folder 36)
  - Lodge 2131, 1923-1973 (Box 45, Folder 37)
  - Lodge 2132, 1922-1974 (Box 45, Folder 38)
  - Lodge 2135, 1936-1969 (Box 45, Folder 39)
  - Lodge 2136, 1930-1974 (Box 45, Folder 40)
  - Lodge 2139, 1944-1973 (Box 45, Folder 41)
- 2140-2179 (Box 46)
  - Lodge 2142, 1925-1972 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 2143, 1921-1974 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 2144, 1959-1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 2146, 1944-1974 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 2147, 1958-1974 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 2148, 1931-1974 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 2149, 1930-1974 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 2150, 1963-1974 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 2151, 1963-1971 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    January 1, 1963-June 30, 1971
  - Lodge 2151, 1971-1974 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    July 1971-July 1974
  - Lodge 2152, 1929-1973 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 2154, 1942-1971 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 2155, 1945-1972 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 2156, 1945-1974 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 2158, 1962-1974 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 2159, 1942-1974 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 2160, 1927-1972 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 2161, 1922-1974 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 2162, 1921-1974 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 2163, 1929-1974 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 2164, 1948-1973 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 2166, 1929-1974 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 2167, 1958-1972 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 2168, 1925-1970 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 2172, 1933-1974 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 2173, 1960-1974 (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 2174, 1944-1969 (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 2175, 1937-1971 (Box 46, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 2176, 1957-1974 (Box 46, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 2177, 1945-1974 (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 2178, 1928-1974 (Box 46, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 2179, 1963-1974 (Box 46, Folder 32)
- 2180-2249 (Box 47)
  - Lodge 2180, 1922-1973 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Lodge 2181, 1929-1974 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Lodge 2182, 1945-1974 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Lodge 2184, 1930-1974 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Lodge 2185, 1923-1973 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Lodge 2186, 1946-1974 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Lodge 2188, 1963-1974 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Lodge 2190, 1931-1974 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Lodge 2192, 1946-1973 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Lodge 2193, 1939-1974 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Lodge 2194, 1924-1974 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Lodge 2195, 1947-1971 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Lodge 2197, 1922-1974 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Lodge 2198, 1946-1974 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Lodge 2202, 1934-1973 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Lodge 2204, 1946-1970 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Lodge 2205, 1921-1974 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Lodge 2207, 1946-1974 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Lodge 2209, 1921-1974 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Lodge 2210, 1922-1974 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Lodge 2211, 1922-1974 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Lodge 2212, 1961-1974 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Lodge 2214, 1946-1974 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Lodge 2216, 1925-1974 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Lodge 2217, 1921-1974 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Lodge 2219, 1963-1969 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Lodge 2219, 1970-1974 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Lodge 2219 - Appeal: Peter Gurovich, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Lodge 2221, 1948-1974 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Lodge 2222, 1945-1971 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Lodge 2224, 1948-1973 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Lodge 2225, 1922-1972 (Box 47, Folder 32)
  - Lodge 2226, 1935-1974 (Box 47, Folder 33)
  - Lodge 2228, 1926-1968 (Box 47, Folder 34)